mimecast.com 2016-12-03

# Privacy Statement | Mimecast

## Privacy Policy

Welcome to Mimecast! Mimecast is a global company, with offices in Europe, North America, Australia and South Africa. We serve companies that have offices in those jurisdictions and across the world. Our website (the "Site"), located at [www.mimecast.com](http://www.mimecast.com/), provides information about our service and is operated by Mimecast Limited. This Privacy Policy describes how Mimecast uses and protects information collected through the Site and our marketing practices generally. To note, if your company engages Mimecast to provide Mimecast’s service, your company and Mimecast will enter into a separate agreement that will, among other things, govern the use of all of the information and data collected and maintained by Mimecast in connection with the operation of the service, including data collected through certain features made available to customers through the Site. Any agreement between your company and Mimecast will take precedence over any conflicting provision in this Privacy Policy. If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or otherwise, you can reach us using the contact information provided below. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time but will use your information only as described in this Privacy Policy at the time your information was collected.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 1st August, 2016.

## Information collected automatically

When you visit the Site, our systems automatically collect certain information about your visit, such as the type of internet browser you use, the website from which you have come to the Site and your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet). We use automatically collected information to assist us in providing and improving the Site and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not use automatically collected information to learn any information about you personally. We may use such information to identify specific companies that are interested in our services and to market to those companies generally.

We (or our vendors) may collect non-personal information using cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, embedded web links, and similar technologies. All of such information tells about how the website is being used and helps us tailor our website to the needs of our visitors. We may receive reports by our vendors on an individual as well as aggregated basis. We do this to improve our marketing and the services we offer you.

We may also use automatically collected information to target advertising for our service on third party sites. For that targeting, we (or our vendors) may use cookies and web beacons to gather information about your activities on the Site in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities on the Site. You can choose to reject certain collection technologies (such as cookies) but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. You can read more about cookies [here](https://www.mimecast.com/cookie-information/). Mimecast does not collect information about your online activities across different web sites, over time. Accordingly, Mimecast does not currently respond to “do not track” browser requests.

Our Site may include certain social media features (such as a “share” or “like” button). Those features are provided by the applicable social media platform (such as Twitter or Facebook). Where information is collected through the social media feature, the use of that information is governed by the privacy policy published by the social media platform that provides the feature.

## Collecting Personal Information

“ **Personal Information** ” is information that is used to identify a discrete individual person. We may collect Personal Information in a variety of ways including:

  * Through web pages on the Site (e.g. when you request a white paper or complete a form for general or partner inquiries);
  * Through responses to an online, email or electronic promotion or survey;
  * Over the telephone.

Such Personal Information may include:

  * Your name, email address, postal address or telephone number;
  * Your title, company name and address;
  * Details of the resources you access on the Site and any data you download;
  * Details of other engagements with Mimecast, such as trade show interactions.

## Using Personal Information

We use your Personal Information in a number of ways including:

  * To assist in responding to your inquiries, including answering your questions on pricing and technical information relating to Mimecast's services;
  * To learn more about your requirements (through surveys and the like) in support of development of our service;
  * To carry out research on our users' demographics;
  * To send you information we think you may find useful about our services;
  * At your request, to subscribe you to our newsletter and alerts concerning the services we provide;
  * To request your opinion and feedback on areas of the Site or in connection with our services.

We may obtain information from third parties to combine with the Personal Information we have gathered as described in this Policy, in order to improve our marketing activities and to ensure the details we hold are relevant and up-to-date. Also, if we provide a means for you to refer a third party to the Site, we may send the third party an email on your behalf with details about the Site.  Mimecast will not use the third party’s information for any other purpose.

You can unsubscribe to emails by following the unsubscribe instructions on any email communications sent to you, or you can email us at [privacy@mimecast.com](mailto:privacy@mimecast.com) or by post at the address provided below.  We provide additional information about your controls below.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * We do not sell or rent Personal Information to third parties.  We do not share Personal Information, except as expressly provided in this Privacy Policy.
  * We may disclose aggregate statistics about visitors to the Site in order to describe our services generally, including on our web site and to prospective partners and other third parties, but these statistics will not include Personal Information.
  * We may disclose your Personal Information to our reseller partners to allow them to provide marketing information on our behalf as described above.
  * We may disclose your Personal Information to service providers who assist us in: (i) website hosting and maintenance; (ii) sending communications; (iii) updating marketing lists and database management; (iv) analyzing data; and (v) in other tasks relevant to the provision of the Site and the marketing of our services. Our service providers will only use your Personal Information to the extent necessary to perform their functions and will be subject to contractual obligations to maintain the security and confidentiality of all information they process.
  * As a worldwide organization, we may share your Personal Information with our affiliates for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.  In addition, in the event of a corporate sale, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Information may be included in the transferred assets.  As a result, the successor of Mimecast may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.
  * We may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by any applicable law or regulation or in response to a legal demand, subpoena, warrant or other similar request.  We may also disclose your Personal Information to any regulatory or law enforcement agency if we believe that such action is necessary to protect the rights, property or personal safety of Mimecast, its customers or any third party.

## Storage and transfer of your Personal Information

At Mimecast, we are committed to maintaining the security of the information we collect from activity on this website and from other marketing efforts. We have therefore implemented technology and security policies and procedures that are intended to reduce the risk of accidental destruction or loss, or the unauthorized disclosure or access to such information.

Please note that information may be collected from this website by any of our affiliates. We may transfer your Personal Information amongst our affiliates, which may process your Personal Information outside the European Economic Area. However, all of our affiliates will process information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and with the Privacy Principles set forth in the EU Data Protection Directive. Mimecast complies with the principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.

The controller of your information is Mimecast Limited or the subsidiary of Mimecast Limited that collected your information.

## Security

We have security measures in place to help protect against the loss or misuse of Personal Information under our control.  Our security practices are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized personnel have access to Personal Information. While we use all reasonable efforts to prevent the loss or misuse of your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of any Personal Information you submit via the Site.

## Public forums

The Site may, from time to time, make blogs, message boards, news groups or other public forums available to its users. Any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when using these and never disclose your Personal Information.  We are not responsible for any Personal Information you post in public forums.

## External links

The Site may, from time to time, contain links to external sites.  We are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites and you should familiarize yourself with such policies upon use of such sites.   

## Your controls

You are in control of the personal information you provide to Mimecast.  You may:

  * Ask for a copy of your personal information;
  * Ask for personal information to be corrected or updated;
  * Ask to remove your personal information from our records

Upon written request, we will provide you with a copy of all of the Personal Information about you that we possess.  Additionally, if you wish to correct or update the Personal Information we hold relating to you or you no longer wish to receive marketing or promotional material, we will make such changes on request. Please see the contact information below.

To note, we will retain your Personal Information for as long as is necessary in keeping with the purposes for which we collect it and to comply with our legal obligations.    

## Contacting us

General Privacy Inquiries:  Please submit any questions, concerns or comments you have about this Privacy Policy or any requests concerning your Personal Information by email to [privacy@mimecast.com](mailto:privacy@mimecast.com).   

Mimecast North America, Inc.  
Attn: Legal Department  
480 Pleasant Street  
Watertown, MA

If your inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed you may contact the following organizations

If you are in North America, contact:

American Arbitration Association Dispute Resolution Process  
800.778.7879  
9AM EST – 8PM EST  
Monday through Friday  
The American Arbitration Association will serve as a liaison with the website to resolve your concerns.

If you are in the UK or Europe contact:

The Information Commissioner’s Office  
Churchill House  
17 Churchill Way  
Cardiff  
CF10 2HH  
029 2067 8400
